<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kielce - CityGuide</string>
    <string name="castle_name">Chęciny Royal Castle</string>
    <string name="castle_desc">Chęciny Royal Castle was built in the late 13th century in Chęciny, Poland. It fell into ruin in the 18th century and remains in that state to this day.</string>
    <string name="bishops_palace_name">Palace of the Kraków Bishops</string>
    <string name="bishops_palace_desc">he Palace of the Kraków Bishops in Kielce (Polish: Pałac Biskupów Krakowskich w Kielcach), was built in the 17th century as a summer residence of Bishops of Kraków in Kielce, Poland. The architecture of the palace constitute a unique mélange of Polish and Italian traditions and reflects political ambitions of its founder. Currently the palace houses a branch of the National Museum with an important gallery of Polish paintings.</string>
    <string name="paradise_cave_name">Paradise Cave</string>
    <string name="paradise_cave_desc">Paradise Cave (Polish: Jaskinia Raj, pronounced Yaskeenya Rye) is a horizontal karstic limestone cave located inside the Malik hill, to the south of Kielce, Świętokrzyskie Voivodship, Poland. It is part of the "Red tourist trail Chęciny - Kielce" in the Świętokrzyskie Mountains</string>
    <string name="kadzielnia_name">Kadzielnia nature reserve</string>
    <string name="kadzielnia_desc">A strict reserve of inanimate nature, area 0.6 ha was established in 1962 after the former quarry. The location of the object makes it one of its kind and the most beautiful place in Poland. With peculiar local rocks containing a rich examples of fossil fauna, coralls or armored fish, some of which were for the first tima founded on Kadzielnia. With the passing of time the rainwater had been dissolving limenstone rock and had formed unique holes, grooves and slots on its surface, and caves within the cliff. Thus, there were 17 caves discovered there, from which some have underground tourist routes. All these pecularities witnesses the fact that about 380 million years ago was flooded with warm waters of prehistoric Devonian sea. The place has become a wonderful natural scenery for an amphitheater with more than five thousand seats, where many occasional events are held. It is here where form more than 20 years the International Scout\'s Festival of Culture of School Youth has been held.</string>
    <string name="slichowice_name">Jan Czarnocki Reserve in Ślichowice</string>
    <string name="slichowice_desc">A strict reserve of rock formation (inanimate nature), area 0.55 ha. Estaablished in 1952. Situated on the edge of a large housing estate. The reserve is a former quarry, located in the western part of the city on the hill Ślichowica.</string>
    <string name="wietrznia_name">Geoeducation Centre - Wietrznia</string>
    <string name="wietrznia_desc">Geoeducation Centre is located in the geological reserve Wietrznia. It constitute a very important point on the Świetokrzyski Archeo-Geological Trail. Exhibition of the centre presents a rich and unique in the world scale collection of animals living in the prehistoric periods, among others while Kielce was flooded with very warm Devonian sea, full of coral reefs.The great attraction is also a time-capsule with 5D cinema, where everyone may take a journeyto the centre of the Earth. Visitors may also take part in field researches, theoretical and practical geoeducational classes, workshops, walks through the paths in the park surrounding the object.</string>
    <string name="bialogon_name">Biesak-Białogon</string>
    <string name="bialogon_desc">Geological semi-reserve, area 13.06 ha. Established in 1981. Situated about 6 km to the south-west of the centre of Kielce, about 1 km south of Krakowska Street (Posłowickie range)</string>
    <string name="karczowka_name">Karczówka</string>
    <string name="karczowka_desc">Landscape semi-reserve, area 26.55 ha. Established in 1953. Situated about 2 km to the west of the centre of Kielce. The best approach from the centre is along Karczówkowska Street.</string>
    <string name="sufraganiec_name">Sufraganiec</string>
    <string name="sufraganiec_desc">A semi-reserve, area 17.31 ha, established in 1961. Near the northern border of the city, between the road by-pass of Kielce (Wiśniówka – Chęciny) and the Kielce – Warsaw railway line. The best road approach along the streets Łódzka and Hubalczyków.</string>
    <string name="da_vinci_name">Science Center Leonardo da Vinci</string>
    <string name="da_vinci_desc">Science Center Leonardo da Vinci is a branch of the Regional Center for Science and Technology. This is a remarkable point on the map Świętokrzyskie region, designed for active recreation and inspiring. It\'s the perfect place for families with children, school groups, active seniors … for all! The main idea of the Center is to arouse interest among the visitors to the natural sciences, through active and creative attitude of strengthening educational activities, topped with delicious fun.</string>
    <string name="korona_kielce_stadion_name">Kielce City Stadium</string>
    <string name="korona_kielce_stadion_desc">The Kolporter Arena (official name) is a multi-purpose stadium in Kielce, Poland. It is currently used mostly for football matches and is the home ground of Korona Kielce. The stadium holds 15,500 and was built in 2006. At the time, it was one of the most modern football stadiums in Poland. </string>
    <string name="yellow_elephant_name">Żólty słoń</string>
</resources>
